Guide to the William T. Cannady Architectural Projects Records, 1956-2018 MS 577
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
William T. Cannady Architectural Projects records
1956-2018
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Cannady, William
MS 577
21.5 Linear Feet (21 boxes and 13 map drawers)
These records include architectural drawings, renderings and project documentation related to the work of William T. Cannady. As a Professor of Architecture at Rice University since 1964, Cannady teaches both undergraduate and graduate design studios, and is a practicing architect.
Biographical/Historical Note
William Cannady is a teacher and practicing architect. As a Professor of Architecture at Rice University since 1964, he teaches both undergraduate and graduate design studios. The undergraduate studio is focused on sustainable design principles applied to real-world projects such as urban mixed-use housing complexes. The graduate Urban Design and Investment Building Design Studio investigates real estate investment projects such as mid-rise, high density, mixed use, mid-town transit oriented developments. This studio provides opportunity for cross discipline collaboration through the use of a wide array of consultants and experts from outside the university and team work with MBA students from Rice's Jones School of Management. Professor Cannady has served as a visiting lecturer and critic at the following institutions: American Academy in Rome; Architectural Association of London; Hydra II Conference, Hydra, Greece; University College London; University of California at Berkeley; University of Kentucky; University of Tennessee; Utah State University; University of Michigan; Texas A & M University; The University of Houston; Texas Tech University; University of Texas at Arlington; Prairie View University; Harvard University; University of Texas at Austin and Iowa State University. In his architectural practice, Cannady has designed and built over two hundred projects, which have been honored with fifty awards, both nationally and locally, for outstanding design. His teaching pedagogy and built work is rooted in the philosophy "the poetry of pragmatism." This approach aspires to preserve tradition while pioneering change. His academic and professional experience covers a wide range of design problems and building types including residential, commercial, institutional and public. His constructed buildings are intended to be easy to build, use, maintain and enjoy. Current projects in Cannady's private practice include a large house on Buffalo Bayou in Houston's River Oaks subdivision; a no-rent, low income, multi-family housing project for the Texas Medical Center; and a major renovation of the Cohen House, the Faculty Club of Rice University.
Scope and Contents
These records include architectural drawings, renderings and project documentation related to the work of William T. Cannady, ranging in date from 1956-2018.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored offsite at the Library Service Center and require 24-hour notice for retrieval. Please contact the Woodson Research Center at 713-348-2586 or woodson@rice.edu for more information.
Access Restrictions
This material is open for research.
Acquisition Note
This material was donated to the Woodson Research Center by Professor Cannady.
Separated Materials
Academic material previously in the Cannady Architectural projects records have been removed to the William T. Cannady academic papers (UA 145).
Index Terms
Subjects
Education; Architecture, American; Architecture -- Texas -- Houston -- 20th century; Architecture; Architects -- Texas; Universities and colleges
- Series I: Projects, 147633
  - Index of University and Professional Experience, 1956-1967; 148076 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Undergraduate Work, Texas A&M, 1956-1960; 148075 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Undergraduate Thesis, UC Berkeley, 1960-1961; 148074 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Graduate Work, Harvard University, 1961-1962; 148073 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Professional Experience, 1960-1962; 148072 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Professional Experience, 1962-1967; 148064 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Wilsey, Ham and Blair - The San Anselmo Town Center Plan, 1961; 148061 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - National School Fallout Design Competition; Awards, January 1963; 148060 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Goleman and Rolfe, Pierce and Pierce - Houston Intercontinental Airport Concept Studies, 1963-1964; 148071 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Goleman and Rolfe, Pierce and Pierce - Houston Intercontinental Airport Preliminary Building Design, 1963-1964; 148070 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Goleman and Rolfe, Pierce and Pierce - Houston Intercontinental Airport, Budget and Financing, 148069 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - City of Port Arthur, 1965-1968; 148163 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Housing Preliminary Design Documents for College of Petroleum and Minerals, Dhahran, Saudi Arabia, Summer 1966; 148066 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - William T. Cannady - Schematic Development Plan, August 1, 1966; 148162 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Caudill Rowlett Scott - A Center for Conferences and Continuing Education, A Report Sponsored by the University City Science Center, October 1966; 148058 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Caudill Rowlett Scott - Ormsby County High School, Carson City, Nevada (Folder 1 of 3), c. 1968; 148054 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Caudill Rowlett Scott - Ormsby County High School, Carson City, Nevada (Folder 2 of 3), c. 1968; 148053 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Caudill Rowlett Scott - Ormsby County High School, Carson City, Nevada (Folder 3 of 3), c. 1968; 148170 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Caudill Rowlett Scott - Arizona State University, Litchfield AZ (folder 1/2), 1968; 148168 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Caudill Rowlett Scott - Arizona State University, Litchfield AZ (folder 2/2), 1968; 148169 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Caudill Rowlett Scott - Building systems components standard detail sheets, 1968; 148165 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Caudill Rowlett Scott - Reston Elementary School, 1968; 147479 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Caudill Rowlett Scott - San Antonio Design Session, May 1968; 147477 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Caudill Rowlett Scott - Delaware Technical and Community College, 1968-1969; 148186 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Caudill Rowlett Scott - Kern County Junior College (folder 1/2), 1968-1969; 148056 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Caudill Rowlett Scott - Kern County Junior College (folder 2/2), 1968-1969; 148187 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Caudill Rowlett Scott - Mixup/Moles Houston, 1968-1969; 148188 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Caudill Rowlett Scott - US Public Health Service Hospital, Galveston, 1968-1969; 148193 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Caudill Rowlett Scott - Block No. 268, Houston, March 1969; 148194 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Caudill Rowlett Scott - Goodyear Blimp Port, 1969; 148195 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Caudill Rowlett Scott - MIDLP, Midland TX, 148196 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Caudill Rowlett Scott - Tenneco properties models photographs, 1969; 148204 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Caudill Rowlett Scott - Design (folder 1/2), 1968-1969; 148197 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Caudill Rowlett Scott - Design (folder 2/2), 1968-1969; 148198 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Caudill Rowlett Scott - Housing, 148199 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Caudill Rowlett Scott - Management, 148200 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Caudill Rowlett Scott - correspondence, New Schools for New Towns, 1968-1969; 148201 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Caudill Rowlett Scott - correspondence, 1968-1969; 148202 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Caudill Rowlett Scott - personal correspondence, 1968-1969; 148203 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - O. Jack Mitchell and William T. Cannady - National Football Hall of Fame entry, 1969; 148205 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Proposed Development - Stony Stratford, Milton Keynes UK, 1969; 148206 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Omniplan - Texas Eastern Transmission Corp., 1970; 148209 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Omniplan - Land of William B. Cox, Jr., development report, San Antonio, September 1970; 148210 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Omniplan - LBJ Library, 1970-1971; 148211 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Omniplan - NCARB New Examination Development (folder 1/2), 1970-1971; 148212 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Omniplan - NCARB New Examination Development (folder 2/2), 1970-1971; 148213 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Omniplan - Eagle Mountain Lake, joint venture, 1970-1972; 148214 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Omniplan - Gifco-Matthews tract site analysis, 1971; 148215 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Omniplan - Houston Surgical Treatment Center, 1971; 148216 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Omniplan - Dallas North Development Property, Preston Rd. at SH 121, 1971-1972; 148217 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Omniplan - Dallas Housing promotion, 1972; 148218 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Omniplan - Imperial Valley Development site analysis, 1972; 148219 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Omniplan - South Jefferson County Civic Center, Port Arthur TX, 1972; 148220 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Omniplan - University Blvd. Ltd., 1972; 148221 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Omniplan - Alpha Housing, undated; 148222 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Omniplan - projects (folder 1/3), 1970-1972; 148223 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Omniplan - projects (folder 2/3), 1970-1972; 148224 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Omniplan - projects (folder 3/3), 1970-1972; 148225 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Omniplan - job list, May 1972; 148226 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Omniplan - Booklets, envelope, folder, cards, 148227 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Omniplan - correspondence/promotion, 1970-1971; 148228 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Omniplan - correspondence, 1970-1971; 148229 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Omniplan - personal correspondence, 1970-1971; 148230 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - William T. Cannady - Cannady House, 1972; 148236 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - William T. Cannady - Jetero Commercial Park, c. 1973; 148231 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - William T. Cannady - housing projects, August 1973; 148232 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - William T. Cannady - Burger Palace, multiple locations, c. 1974; 148237 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - William T. Cannady - Military Hospital, Damascus Syria, 1974; 148233 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - William T. Cannady - Shami Hospital, Damascus Syria, 1974; 148234 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - William T. Cannady - office retail complex, Bahrain, 1974; 148235 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - William T. Cannady - Crane House, February 1974; 148238 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - William T. Cannady - Camellia Pointe and Azalea Trails planning and design report, May 1974; 148239 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - William T. Cannady - Children's Mental Health Services of Houston, 1974-1977; 148240 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Anderson Todd and William Cannady - renovation of Baker, Hanszen, and Will Rice Colleges for Rice University, 1974; 148242 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Anderson Todd and William Cannady - proposed additions to Cohen House, Rice University, 1975; 148243 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Anderson Todd and William Cannady - Bayou House, 1979; 148247 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Cannady-Brown Partnership - Goldsmith Townhouses, August 1976; 148248 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates - Saint Barnabas Episcopal Church (folder 1/3), 1964-1969; 148207 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates - Saint Barnabas Episcopal Church (folder 2/3), to 1971; 148208 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates - Saint Barnabas Episcopal Church (folder 3/3), 172208
  - William T. Cannady and Associates - Commons Townhouses, May 1972; 148244 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates - Brochstein House, 1973; 148245 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates - The Khamees Manor Luxury Apartments, Abu Dhabi UAE, 1974; 148246 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates - proposal for Duchesne Academy gymnasium project, January 1976; 148249 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates - University Center, a proposal for the development of a mixed-use center at University Blvd. and Greenbriar, January 1976; 148250 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates - proposal, capital improvements at Baytown Health Center, 1977; 148251 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates - Augusta Oaks Townhomes project description, January 1977; 148252 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates - Lovett Square (1/2), 1977-1980; 148253 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates - Lovett Square (2/2), 172209
  - William T. Cannady and Associates - Sunset Terrace, c. 1978; 148254 (Box 4a, Folder 1)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates - Cannady Ranch, Walhalla, Round Top TX, 1979; 148255 (Box 4a, Folder 2)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates - Eastwood Park, 1979; 148256 (Box 4a, Folder 3)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates - Kirby Building Systems office expansion, c. 1979; 148257 (Box 4a, Folder 4)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates - Church of the Good Shepherd, Friendswood TX, July 1980; 148258 (Box 4a, Folder 5)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates - Port Arthur Cultural Resource Center, c. 1981; 148259 (Box 4a, Folder 6)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates - Sid W. Richardson Institute for Preventative Medicine, c. 1981; 148260 (Box 4a, Folder 7)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates - Baylor College of Medicine housing study, June 15, 1981; 148261 (Box 4a, Folder 8)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates - Benjamin Franklin Savings and Loan Association, c. 1982; 148262 (Box 4a, Folder 9)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates - Benjamin Franklin Savings and Loan Association (2/2), 172210 (Box 4a, Folder 10)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates - Methodist Hospital Pathology Department renovation and expansion, 1982; 148263 (Box 4a, Folder 11)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates - Fayette County Savings and Loan Association, La Grange TX, 1983; 148264 (Box 4a, Folder 12)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates - Architect's Office, Houston TX, 1984; 148265 (Box 4a, Folder 13)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates - Blake House, Big Lake LA, 1985; 148266 (Box 4a, Folder 14)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates - Chocolate Bayou Theater, 1985; 148267 (Box 4a, Folder 15)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates - The Mayan Group brochure and photograph of Cannady's Chez Eddie, 1985; 148268 (Box 4a, Folder 16)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates - Stanford Plaza, Springfield MO, 1985; 148269 (Box 4a, Folder 17)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates - Village Square, c. 1985; 148270 (Box 4a, Folder 18)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates - Village Square II, 170080 (Box 4a, Folder 19)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates - Riedel House, ca. 1981; 172491 (Box 4a, Folder 20)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates - Christ the King Episcopal Church, Alief, Texas, 172493 (Box 4a, Folder 21)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates - Texas Department of Corrections, Officer's Training Academy, 1982; 172495 (Box 4a, Folder 22)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates for Stanford Associates - Eaglepointe Apartments/Townhomes, Colorado Springs CO, 1983-1984; 148271 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates for Stanford Associates - Gleneagles Apartments, Colorado Springs CO, 1984; 148272 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates for Stanford Associates - Chardonnay Apartments, Springfield MO, 1985; 148273 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates for Stanford Associates - Falcon Point Condominiums, Colorado Springs CO, 1985; 148274 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates for Stanford Associates - Windchime Center, Colorado Springs CO, 1985; 148275 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates - Darlington Project, Atlanta GA, c. 1986; 148276 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates - Wyndham Garden Hotels, 1989-1990, undated; 148277 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates - proposal, renovations and additions to Hamman Hall, Rice University, December 1990; 148278 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates / Willis, Bricker and Cannady - Northern Trust Bank (+ CED News information), c. 1993; 148279 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates / Willis, Bricker and Cannady - EB Cape Center for Public Works Excellence (+ CED News information), c. 1995-1996; 148280 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates - Building over Ravines, Creeks, Rivers, and other Water Courses, February 1996; 148282 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates - 2365 Rice Blvd., Houston TX, undated; 148283 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates - 6135 Kirby Dr., Houston TX, undated; 148284 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates - Cannady House II, Houston TX, undated; 148285 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates - Church of the Good Shepherd, Tomball TX, undated; 148286 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates - David Taylor Classics Car Museum, Galveston TX, undated; 148287 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates - photos and index, 1975; 148288 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates - resumes, project list, company profile, images, and booklets, c. 1977-1984; 148289 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Cannady, Jackson and Ryan - selected project experience, architect experience, 1972-1989; 148290 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Cannady, Jackson and Ryan - Philadelphia Museum of Art, drawings of other art museums, 1983-1987; 148291 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Cannady, Jackson and Ryan - Schulte House, Round Top TX, 1986; 148292 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Cannady, Jackson and Ryan - Windward Conference Resort, Scottsdale AZ, c. 1986; 148293 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Cannady, Jackson and Ryan - Market Square project proposal, Louisville KY, c. 1987; 148294 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Cannady, Jackson and Ryan - SPCA building architectural drawings, October 15, 1987; 148295 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Cannady, Jackson and Ryan - King House, Fripp Island SC, 1988; 148296 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Cannady, Jackson and Ryan - A house for Lot X in Shadyside, Houston TX, c. 1988-1991; 148297 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Cannady, Jackson and Ryan - The Children's Museum of Houston, c. 1989-1990; 148298 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Cannady, Jackson and Ryan - Philadelphia Museum of Art, Level 1 Section 5 gallery reinstallation, c. 1990; 148299 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Cannady, Jackson and Ryan - announcement of opening of new practice, c. 1986; 148300 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Cannady, Jackson and Ryan - Nonresidential Wood Design Award Program, American Wood Council, 1987; 148301 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Cannady, Jackson and Ryan - Wood Design Award Program, American Wood Council, 1988; 148302 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Cannady, Jackson and Ryan - Architects' Qualification Statement, June 1, 1988; 148303 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Willis, Bricker and Cannady - Houses Architects Build for Themselves, May 1, 1997; 148304 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Willis, Bricker and Cannady - The 1905 CF Marschner Building, dedication and open house, June 7, 1997; 148305 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Willis, Bricker and Cannady - Hermann Professional Building renovation, Houston TX, c. 1998; 148306 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Willis, Bricker and Cannady - Jones Plaza, Houston TX, 1999; 148307 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Bricker and Cannady - University of Houston Downtown renovation, 1998-2002; 148308 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Bricker and Cannady - Morian residence, undated; 148309 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Piney Point Estates property, c. 1972; 148310 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Amigos de las Americas, Houston TX, c. 1973; 148311 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - American International Design Associates, proposal for hotel in Abu Dhabi/Muscat, 1974; 148312 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Request for proposals, Harris County Hospital District, February 18, 1977; 148313 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Parker Estate, c. 1979; 148314 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Allen House - sketches, April 5, 1984; 148316 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Schnitzer House - architectural drawings, 1985; 148317 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Texas Wesleyan University, West Library - drawing reproduction, c. 1986; 148318 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Blimport photograph, Roma, December 26, 1989; 148319 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Proposed subdivision of lot 2, Remington Lane, 1992; 148457 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - World Savings and Loan, Kingwood TX, 1992; 148320 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Griffith House - architectural drawings, c. 1997; 148321 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Arts and Humanities Project in the Southeast, undated; 148322 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - House for Hakeem Olajuwon, Sugar Land TX, undated; 148323 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Villa, Istanbul Turkey, undated; 148324 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Landscape drawings, undated; 148325 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Principal Architectural Projects - list and images, 1972-1982; 147489 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Cannady portfolio, to 1982; 148458 (Box 5, Folder 57)
- Series II: Sketches, awards, files, and other papers, 147486
  - Sketches, 1978; 148459 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Sketch - From Font. Paoli, Rome, April 4, 1978; 147521 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Sketch - Piazza de S. Pietro, Rome, April 5, 1978; 147520 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Sketch - Trastevere, April 10, 1978; 147519 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Sketch - Piazza dei Signori, Verona, June 10, 1981; 147518 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Sketch - Villa Rotunda, Vincenza, June 12, 1981; 147517 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Sketch - Parthenon, July 22, 1983; 147516 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Sketch - Villa di Papa Giulia, Rome, February 21, 1986; 147515 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Homes for Better Living Awards/AIA Honor Awards program forms and materials - Cannady Ranch House, Round Top TX, 1981, 1982; 148460 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - AIA Honor Awards Program descriptive data and materials - Fayette County Savings and Loans Association, 1986; 148461 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Award - AIA Houston Chapter - Architectural Excellence - Saint Barnabas Episcopal Church, August 1968; 147512 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Award - The Texas Society of Architects - Honor Award to Saint Barnabas Episcopal Church, October 29, 1970; 147511 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Award - AIA Houston Chapter - Award of Honor for Architectural Excellence - Cannady House, December 15, 1972; 147510 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Award - AIA Houston Chapter - Award of Honor, Excellence in Residential Design - Walker's Mark Townhouses, 1978; 147509 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Award - AIA Houston Chapter - Houston Home and Garden/Houston Residential Design Award of Honor for Architectural Excellence in Residential Design - Sunset Terrace, 1980; 147508 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Award - AIA Houston Chapter - Houston Home and Garden/Houston Home Design Award of Honor for Architectural Excellence in Residential Design - Lovett Square, 1980; 147507 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Award - AIA Houston Chapter - Houston Home and Garden/Houston Home Design Award of Honor for Architectural Excellence in Residential Design - Weekend Country House, Round Top TX, 1981; 147506 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Award - AIA Houston Chapter - Silver Honor Award, Excellence in Interior Architecture - Methodist Hospital, Sid W. Richardson Institute for Preventive Medicine, October 19, 1982; 147505 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Award - AIA Houston Chapter - Architecture Honorable Mention - Fayette Savings Association, La Grange TX, October 22, 1984; 147504 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Award - AIA Houston Chapter - Architecture Honorable Mention - Cannady House Addition, October 22, 1984; 147503 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Award - First Awards for Innovative Remodeling of a Residential Structure - Honor Award, 1984; 147502 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Award - First Awards for Innovative Remodeling of a Commercial Structure - Village Square, 1985; 147501 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Award - AIA Houston Chapter - Unbuilt Projects Honor Award - Wm. D. Blake Summer Home, Lake Charles LA, November 24, 1986; 147500 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Award - AIA Houston Chapter - Architecture Honor Award - Schulte Ranch, Round Top TX, September 19, 1988; 147499 (Box 6, Folder 24)